Jensen, Vernon Collection of International Longshoremen's Association's and Brotherhood of Locomotive Firemen and Enginemen's Materials 5487
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Vernon Jensen Collection of International Longshoremen's Association's and Brotherhood of Locomotive Firemen and Enginemen's Materials
1953-1975
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Jensen, Vernon H.
5487
3 cubic feet
3 linear ft.
Articles, reports, pamphlets, newsletters, publications.
Issues of the Maritime Reporter from August 1, 1967, through September 30, 1971; October 1, 1971; and January 31, 1975.
5727056
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, October 23, 2013
EAD encoding:
Kheel Staff, April 03, 2015
Biographical / Historical
Vernon Jensen (July 10, 1907 September 27, 1998) was a founding faculty member of Cornell's New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations.
A graduate of Brigham Young University (BS '32), Jensen worked as a substitute teacher in Salt Lake City after college before leaving to pursue graduate study at the University of California at Berkeley (PhD '39). Shortly before completing his degree, Jensen began teaching at the University of Colorado. He taught at UC from 1937 to 1946, during which time he also served as a consultant to the National Defense Mediation Board (1941) and a public panel member, mediator and arbitrator for the National War Labor Board (1942) and Wage Stabilization Director of the NWLB's Ninth Region (1942-1944).
Jensen was among the founding faculty of the School of Industrial and Labor Relations, joining Cornell in 1946. Jensen became Associate Dean of the ILR School in 1965 and was elected to Cornell's Board of Trustees in 1973. In addition to numerous articles, Jensen wrote four books, Lumber and Labor (1945), Heritage of Conflict (1950), Collective Bargaining in the Nonferrous Metal Industry (1955), and Hiring of Dockworkers and Employment Practices in the Ports of New York, London, Liverpool, Rotterdam, and Marseilles (1964).
Scope and Contents
Issues of the Maritime Reporter from August 1, 1967, through September 30, 1971; October 1, 1971; and January 31, 1975.
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
5727056
- Todd Daily Maritime, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  Scope and Contents
  August
  - Item 1: Todd Daily Maritime, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    Author: Todd ShipBuilding Co.
    Notes: no.67-145 (1967: Aug. 1)
    Format: Publication
    Language: English.
  - Item 2: Todd Daily Maritime, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    Notes: no.67-146 (1967: Aug. 2)
  - Item 3: Todd Daily Maritime, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    Notes: no.67-147 (1967: Aug. 3)
  - Item 4: Todd Daily Maritime, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    Notes: no.67-148 (1967: Aug. 4)
  - Item 5: Todd Daily Maritime, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    Notes: no.67-149 (1967: Aug. 7)
  - Item 6: Todd Daily Maritime, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    Notes: no.67-150 (1967: Aug. 8)
  - Item 7: Todd Daily Maritime, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    Notes: no.67-151 (1967: Aug. 9)
  - Item 8: Todd Daily Maritime, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    Notes: no.67-152 (1967: Aug. 10)
  - Item 9: Todd Daily Maritime, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    Notes: no.67-153 (1967: Aug. 11)
  - Item 10: Todd Daily Maritime, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    Notes: no.67-154 (1967: Aug. 14)
  - Item 11: Todd Daily Maritime, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    Notes: no.67-155 (1967: Aug. 15)
  - Item 12: Todd Daily Maritime, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    Notes: no.67-156 (1967: Aug. 16)
  - Item 13: Todd Daily Maritime, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    Notes: no.67-157 (1967: Aug. 17)
  - Item 14: Todd Daily Maritime, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    Notes: no.67-158 (1967: Aug. 18)
  - Item 15: Todd Daily Maritime, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    Notes: no.67-159 (1967: Aug. 21)
  - Item 16: Todd Daily Maritime, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    Notes: no.67-160 (1967: Aug. 22)
  - Item 17: Todd Daily Maritime, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    Notes: no.67-161 (1967: Aug. 23)
  - Item 18: Todd Daily Maritime, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    Notes: no.67-162 (1967: Aug. 24)
  - Item 19: Todd Daily Maritime, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    Notes: no.67-163 (1967: Aug. 25)
  - Item 20: Todd Daily Maritime, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    Notes: no.67-164 (1967: Aug. 28)
  - Item 21: Todd Daily Maritime, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    Notes: no.67-165 (1967: Aug. 29)
  - Item 22: Todd Daily Maritime, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    Notes: no.67-166 (1967: Aug. 30)
  - Item 23: Todd Daily Maritime, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    Notes: no.67-167 (1967: Aug. 31)
- Todd Daily Maritime, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  September
  - Item 1: Todd Daily Maritime, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    Notes: no.67-168 (1967: Sep. 1)
  - Item 2: Todd Daily Maritime, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    Notes: no.67-169 (1967: Sep. 5)
  - Item 3: Todd Daily Maritime, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    Notes: no.67-170 (1967: Sep. 6)
  - Item 4: Todd Daily Maritime, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    Notes: no.67-171 (1967: Sep. 7)
  - Item 5: Todd Daily Maritime, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    Notes: no.67-172 (1967: Sep. 8)
  - Item 6: Todd Daily Maritime, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    Notes: no.67-173 (1967: Sep. 11)
  - Item 7: Todd Daily Maritime, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    Notes: no.67-174 (1967: Sep. 12)
  - Item 8: Todd Daily Maritime, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    Notes: no.67-175 (1967: Sep. 13)
  - Item 9: Todd Daily Maritime, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    Notes: no.67-176 (1967: Sep. 14)
  - Item 10: Todd Daily Maritime, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    Notes: no.67-177 (1967: Sep. 15)
  - Item 11: Todd Daily Maritime, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    Notes: no.67-178 (1967: Sep. 18)
  - Item 12: Todd Daily Maritime, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    Notes: no.67-179 (1967: Sep. 19)
  - Item 13: Todd Daily Maritime, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    Notes: no.67-180 (1967: Sep. 20)
  - Item 14: Todd Daily Maritime, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    Notes: no.67-181 (1967: Sep. 21)
  - Item 15: Todd Daily Maritime, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    Notes: no.67-182 (1967: Sep. 22)
  - Item 16: Todd Daily Maritime, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    Notes: no.67-183 (1967: Sep. 25)
  - Item 17: Todd Daily Maritime, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    Notes: no.67-184 (1967: Sep. 26)
  - Item 18: Todd Daily Maritime, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    Notes: no.67-185 (1967: Sep. 27)
  - Item 19: Todd Daily Maritime, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    Notes: no.67-186 (1967: Sep. 28)
  - Item 20: Todd Daily Maritime, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    Notes: no.67-187 (1967: Sep. 29)
- Todd Daily Maritime, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  October
  - Item 1: Todd Daily Maritime, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    Notes: no.67-188 (1967: Oct. 2)
  - Item 2: Todd Daily Maritime, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    Notes: no.67-189 (1967: Oct. 3)
  - Item 3: Todd Daily Maritime, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    Notes: no.67-190 (1967: Oct. 4)
  - Item 4: Todd Daily Maritime, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    Notes: no.67-191 (1967: Oct. 5)
  - Item 5: Todd Daily Maritime, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    Notes: no.67-192 (1967: Oct. 6)
  - Item 6: Todd Daily Maritime, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    Notes: no.67-193 (1967: Oct. 9)
  - Item 7: Todd Daily Maritime, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    Notes: no.67-194 (1967: Oct. 10)
  - Item 8: Todd Daily Maritime, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    Notes: no.67-195 (1967: Oct. 11)
  - Item 9: Todd Daily Maritime, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    Notes: no.67-196 (1967: Oct. 13)
  - Item 10: Todd Daily Maritime, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    Notes: no.67-197 (1967: Oct. 16)
  - Item 11: Todd Daily Maritime, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    Notes: no.67-198 (1967: Oct. 17)
  - Item 12: Todd Daily Maritime, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    Notes: no.67-199 (1967: Oct. 18)
  - Item 13: Todd Daily Maritime, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    Notes: no.67-200 (1967: Oct. 19)
  - Item 14: Todd Daily Maritime, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    Notes: no.67-201 (1967: Oct. 20)
  - Item 15: Todd Daily Maritime, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    Notes: no.67-202 (1967: Oct. 23)
  - Item 16: Todd Daily Maritime, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    Notes: no.67-203 (1967: Oct. 24)
  - Item 17: Todd Daily Maritime, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    Notes: no.67-204 (1967: Oct. 25)
  - Item 18: Todd Daily Maritime, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    Notes: no.67-205 (1967: Oct. 26)
  - Item 19: Todd Daily Maritime, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    Notes: no.67-206 (1967: Oct. 27)
  - Item 20: Todd Daily Maritime, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    Notes: no.67-207 (1967: Oct. 30)
  - Item 21: Todd Daily Maritime, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    Notes: no.67-208 (1967: Oct. 31)
- Todd Daily Maritime, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  November
  - Item 1: Todd Daily Maritime, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    Notes: no.67-209 (1967: Nov. 1)
  - Item 2: Todd Daily Maritime, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    Notes: no.67-210 (1967: Nov. 2)
  - Item 3: Todd Daily Maritime, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    Notes: no.67-211 (1967: Nov. 3)
  - Item 4: Todd Daily Maritime, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    Notes: no.67-211 (1967: Nov. 6)
  - Item 5: Todd Daily Maritime, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    Notes: no.67-212 (1967: Nov. 8)
  - Item 6: Todd Daily Maritime, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    Notes: no.67-213 (1967: Nov. 9)
  - Item 7: Todd Daily Maritime, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    Notes: no.67-214 (1967: Nov. 10)
  - Item 8: Todd Daily Maritime, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    Notes: no.67-215 (1967: Nov. 13)
  - Item 9: Todd Daily Maritime, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    Notes: no.67-216 (1967: Nov. 14)
  - Item 10: Todd Daily Maritime, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    Notes: no.67-217 (1967: Nov. 15)
  - Item 11: Todd Daily Maritime, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    Notes: no.67-218 (1967: Nov. 16)
  - Item 12: Todd Daily Maritime, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    Notes: no.67-218 (1967: Nov. 17)
  - Item 13: Todd Daily Maritime, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    Notes: no.67-219 (1967: Nov. 20)
  - Item 14: Todd Daily Maritime, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    Notes: no.67-220 (1967: Nov. 21)
  - Item 15: Todd Daily Maritime, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    Notes: no.67-221 (1967: Nov. 22)
  - Item 16: Todd Daily Maritime, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    Notes: no.67-222 (1967: Nov. 24)
  - Item 17: Todd Daily Maritime, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    Notes: no.67-223 (1967: Nov. 27)
  - Item 18: Todd Daily Maritime, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    Notes: no.67-224 (1967: Nov. 28)
  - Item 19: Todd Daily Maritime, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    Notes: no.67-225 (1967: Nov. 29)
  - Item 20: Todd Daily Maritime, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    Notes: no.67-226 (1967: Nov. 30)
- Todd Daily Maritime, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  December
  - Item 1: Todd Daily Maritime, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    Notes: no.67-227 (1967: Dec. 1)
  - Item 2: Todd Daily Maritime, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    Notes: no.67-228 (1967: Dec. 4)
  - Item 3: Todd Daily Maritime, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    Notes: no.67-228 (1967: Dec. 5)
  - Item 4: Todd Daily Maritime, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    Notes: no.67-229 (1967: Dec. 6)
  - Item 5: Todd Daily Maritime, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    Notes: no.67-230 (1967: Dec. 7)
  - Item 6: Todd Daily Maritime, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    Notes: no.67-231 (1967: Dec. 8)
  - Item 7: Todd Daily Maritime, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    Notes: no.67-232 (1967: Dec. 11)
  - Item 8: Todd Daily Maritime, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    Notes: no.67-233 (1967: Dec. 12)
  - Item 9: Todd Daily Maritime, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    Notes: no.67-234 (1967: Dec. 13)
  - Item 10: Todd Daily Maritime, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    Notes: no.67-235 (1967: Dec. 14)
  - Item 11: Todd Daily Maritime, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    Notes: no.67-236 (1967: Dec. 15)
  - Item 12: Todd Daily Maritime, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    Notes: no.67-237 (1967: Dec. 18)
  - Item 13: Todd Daily Maritime, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    Notes: no.67-238 (1967: Dec. 19)
  - Item 14: Todd Daily Maritime, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    Notes: no.67-239 (1967: Dec. 20)
  - Item 15: Todd Daily Maritime, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    Notes: no.67-240 (1967: Dec. 21)
  - Item 16: Todd Daily Maritime, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    Notes: no.67-241 (1967: Dec. 22)
  - Item 17: Todd Daily Maritime, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    Notes: no.67-242 (1967: Dec. 26)
  - Item 18: Todd Daily Maritime, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    Notes: no.67-243 (1967: Dec. 27)
  - Item 19: Todd Daily Maritime, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    Notes: no.67-244 (1967: Dec. 28)
  - Item 20: Todd Daily Maritime, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    Notes: no.67-245 (1967: Dec. 29)
- Todd Daily Maritime, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  January
  - Item 1: Todd Daily Maritime, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    Notes: no.67-1 (1968: Jan. 2)
  - Item 2: Todd Daily Maritime, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    Notes: no.67-2 (1968: Jan. 3)
  - Item 3: Todd Daily Maritime, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    Notes: no.67-3 (1968: Jan. 4)
  - Item 4: Todd Daily Maritime, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    Notes: no.67-4 (1968: Jan. 5)
  - Item 5: Todd Daily Maritime, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    Notes: no.68-5 (1968: Jan. 8)
  - Item 6: Todd Daily Maritime, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    Notes: no.68-6 (1968: Jan. 9)
  - Item 7: Todd Daily Maritime, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    Notes: no.68-7 (1968: Jan. 10)
  - Item 8: Todd Daily Maritime, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    Notes: no.68-8 (1968: Jan. 11)
  - Item 9: Todd Daily Maritime, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    Notes: no.68-9 (1968: Jan. 12)
  - Item 10: Todd Daily Maritime, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    Notes: no.68-9 (1968: Jan. 15)
  - Item 11: Todd Daily Maritime, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    Notes: no.68-10 (1968: Jan. 16)
  - Item 12: Todd Daily Maritime, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    Notes: no.68-11 (1968: Jan. 17)
  - Item 13: Todd Daily Maritime, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    Notes: no.68-12 (1968: Jan. 18)
  - Item 14: Todd Daily Maritime, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    Notes: no.68-13 (1968: Jan. 19)
  - Item 15: Todd Daily Maritime, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    Notes: no.68-14 (1968: Jan. 22)
  - Item 16: Todd Daily Maritime, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    Notes: no.68-15 (1968: Jan. 23)
  - Item 17: Todd Daily Maritime, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    Notes: no.68-16 (1968: Jan. 24)
  - Item 18: Todd Daily Maritime, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    Notes: no.68-17 (1968: Jan. 25)
  - Item 19: Todd Daily Maritime, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    Notes: no.68-18 (1968: Jan. 26)
  - Item 20: Todd Daily Maritime, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    Notes: no.68-19 (1968: Jan. 29)
  - Item 21: Todd Daily Maritime, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    Notes: no.68-20 (1968: Jan. 30)
  - Item 22: Todd Daily Maritime, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    Notes: no.68-21 (1968: Jan. 31)
- Todd Daily Maritime, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  February
  - Item 1: Todd Daily Maritime, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    Notes: no.68-22 (1968: Feb. 1)
  - Item 2: Todd Daily Maritime, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    Notes: no.68-23 (1968: Feb. 2)
  - Item 3: Todd Daily Maritime, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    Notes: no.68-24 (1968: Feb. 5)
  - Item 4: Todd Daily Maritime, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    Notes: no.68-25 (1968: Feb. 6)
  - Item 5: Todd Daily Maritime, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    Notes: no.68-26 (1968: Feb. 7)
  - Item 6: Todd Daily Maritime, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    Notes: no.68-27 (1968: Feb. 8)
  - Item 7: Todd Daily Maritime, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    Notes: no.68-28 (1968: Feb. 9)
  - Item 8: Todd Daily Maritime, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    Notes: no.68-29 (1968: Feb. 13)
  - Item 9: Todd Daily Maritime, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    Notes: no.68-30 (1968: Feb. 14)
  - Item 10: Todd Daily Maritime, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    Notes: no.68-31 (1968: Feb. 15)
  - Item 11: Todd Daily Maritime, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    Notes: no.68-32 (1968: Feb. 16)
  - Item 12: Todd Daily Maritime, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    Notes: no.68-33 (1968: Feb. 19)
  - Item 13: Todd Daily Maritime, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    Notes: no.68-34 (1968: Feb. 20)
  - Item 14: Todd Daily Maritime, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    Notes: no.68-35 (1968: Feb. 21)
  - Item 15: Todd Daily Maritime, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    Notes: no.68-36 (1968: Feb. 23)
  - Item 16: Todd Daily Maritime, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    Notes: no.68-37 (1968: Feb. 26)
  - Item 17: Todd Daily Maritime, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    Notes: no.68-38 (1968: Feb. 27)
  - Item 18: Todd Daily Maritime, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    Notes: no.68-39 (1968: Feb. 28)
  - Item 19: Todd Daily Maritime, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    Notes: no.68-40 (1968: Feb. 29)
- Todd Daily Maritime, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  March
  - Item 1: Todd Daily Maritime, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    Notes: no.68-41 (1968: Mar. 1)
  - Item 2: Todd Daily Maritime, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    Notes: no.68-42 (1968: Mar. 4)
  - Item 3: Todd Daily Maritime, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    Notes: no.68-43 (1968: Mar. 5)
  - Item 4: Todd Daily Maritime, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    Notes: no.68-44 (1968: Mar. 6)
  - Item 5: Todd Daily Maritime, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    Notes: no.68-45 (1968: Mar. 7)
  - Item 6: Todd Daily Maritime, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    Notes: no.68-46 (1968: Mar. 8)
  - Item 7: Todd Daily Maritime, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    Notes: no.68-47 (1968: Mar. 11)
  - Item 8: Todd Daily Maritime, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    Notes: no.68-48 (1968: Mar. 12)
  - Item 9: Todd Daily Maritime, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    Notes: no.68-49 (1968: Mar. 13)
  - Item 10: Todd Daily Maritime, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    Notes: no.68-50 (1968: Mar. 14)
  - Item 11: Todd Daily Maritime, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    Notes: no.68-51 (1968: Mar. 15)
  - Item 12: Todd Daily Maritime, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    Notes: no.68-52 (1968: Mar. 18)
  - Item 13: Todd Daily Maritime, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    Notes: no.68-53 (1968: Mar. 19)
  - Item 14: Todd Daily Maritime, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    Notes: no.68-54 (1968: Mar. 20)
  - Item 15: Todd Daily Maritime, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    Notes: no.68-55 (1968: Mar. 21)
  - Item 16: Todd Daily Maritime, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    Notes: no.68-56 (1968: Mar. 22)
  - Item 17: Todd Daily Maritime, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    Notes: no.68-57 (1968: Mar. 25)
  - Item 18: Todd Daily Maritime, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    Notes: no.68-58 (1968: Mar. 26)
  - Item 19: Todd Daily Maritime, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    Notes: no.68-59 (1968: Mar. 27)
  - Item 20: Todd Daily Maritime, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    Notes: no.68-60 (1968: Mar. 28)
  - Item 21: Todd Daily Maritime, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    Notes: no.68-61 (1968: Mar. 29)
- Todd Daily Maritime, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  April
  - Item 1: Todd Daily Maritime, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    Notes: no.68-62 (1968: Apr. 1)
  - Item 2: Todd Daily Maritime, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    Notes: no.68-63 (1968: Apr. 2)
  - Item 3: Todd Daily Maritime, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    Notes: no.68-64 (1968: Apr. 3)
  - Item 4: Todd Daily Maritime, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    Notes: no.68-65 (1968: Apr. 4)
  - Item 5: Todd Daily Maritime, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    Notes: no.68-66 (1968: Apr. 5)
  - Item 6: Todd Daily Maritime, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    Notes: no.68-67 (1968: Apr. 8)
  - Item 7: Todd Daily Maritime, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    Notes: no.68-68 (1968: Apr. 9)
  - Item 8: Todd Daily Maritime, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    Notes: no.68-69 (1968: Apr. 10)
  - Item 9: Todd Daily Maritime, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    Notes: no.68-70 (1968: Apr. 11)
  - Item 10: Todd Daily Maritime, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    Notes: no.68-71 (1968: Apr. 12)
  - Item 11: Todd Daily Maritime, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    Notes: no.68-72 (1968: Apr. 15)
  - Item 12: Todd Daily Maritime, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    Notes: no.68-73 (1968: Apr. 16)
  - Item 13: Todd Daily Maritime, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    Notes: no.68-74 (1968: Apr. 17)
  - Item 14: Todd Daily Maritime, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    Notes: no.68-75 (1968: Apr. 18)
  - Item 15: Todd Daily Maritime, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    Notes: no.68-76 (1968: Apr. 19)
  - Item 16: Todd Daily Maritime, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    Notes: no.68-77 (1968: Apr. 22)
  - Item 17: Todd Daily Maritime, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    Notes: no.68-78 (1968: Apr. 23)
  - Item 18: Todd Daily Maritime, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    Notes: no.68-79 (1968: Apr. 24)
  - Item 19: Todd Daily Maritime, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    Notes: no.68-80 (1968: Apr. 25)
  - Item 20: Todd Daily Maritime, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    Notes: no.68-81 (1968: Apr. 26)
  - Item 21: Todd Daily Maritime, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    Notes: no.68-82 (1968: Apr. 29)
  - Item 22: Todd Daily Maritime, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    Notes: no.68-83 (1968: Apr. 30)
- Todd Daily Maritime, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  May
  - Item 1: Todd Daily Maritime, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    Notes: no.68-84 (1968: May 1)
  - Item 2: Todd Daily Maritime, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    Notes: no.68-85 (1968: May 2)
  - Item 3: Todd Daily Maritime, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    Notes: no.68-86 (1968: May 3)
  - Item 4: Todd Daily Maritime, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    Notes: no.68-87 (1968: May 6)
  - Item 5: Todd Daily Maritime, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    Notes: no.68-88 (1968: May 7)
  - Item 6: Todd Daily Maritime, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    Notes: no.68-89 (1968: May 8)
  - Item 7: Todd Daily Maritime, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    Notes: no.68-90 (1968: May 9)
  - Item 8: Todd Daily Maritime, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    Notes: no.68-91 (1968: May 10)
  - Item 9: Todd Daily Maritime, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    Notes: no.68-92 (1968: May 13)
  - Item 10: Todd Daily Maritime, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    Notes: no.68-93 (1968: May 14)
  - Item 11: Todd Daily Maritime, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    Notes: no.68-94 (1968: May 15)
  - Item 12: Todd Daily Maritime, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    Notes: no.68-95 (1968: May 16)
  - Item 13: Todd Daily Maritime, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    Notes: no.68-96 (1968: May 17)
  - Item 14: Todd Daily Maritime, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    Notes: no.68-97 (1968: May 20)
  - Item 15: Todd Daily Maritime, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    Notes: no.68-98 (1968: May 21)
  - Item 16: Todd Daily Maritime, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    Notes: no.68-99 (1968: May 22)
  - Item 17: Todd Daily Maritime, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    Notes: no.68-100 (1968: May 23)
  - Item 18: Todd Daily Maritime, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    Notes: no.68-101 (1968: May 24)
  - Item 19: Todd Daily Maritime, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    Notes: no.68-102 (1968: May 27)
  - Item 20: Todd Daily Maritime, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    Notes: no.68-103 (1968: May 28)
  - Item 21: Todd Daily Maritime, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    Notes: no.68-104 (1968: May 29)
  - Item 22: Todd Daily Maritime, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    Notes: no.68-105 (1968: May 31)
- Todd Daily Maritime, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  June
  - Item 1: Todd Daily Maritime, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    Notes: no.68-106 (1968: June 3)
  - Item 2: Todd Daily Maritime, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    Notes: no.68-107 (1968: June 4)
  - Item 3: Todd Daily Maritime, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    Notes: no.68-108 (1968: June 5)
  - Item 4: Todd Daily Maritime, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    Notes: no.68-110 (1968: June 7)
  - Item 5: Todd Daily Maritime, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    Notes: no.68-111 (1968: June 10)
  - Item 6: Todd Daily Maritime, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    Notes: no.68-112 (1968: June 11)
  - Item 7: Todd Daily Maritime, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    Notes: no.68-114 (1968: June 12)
  - Item 8: Todd Daily Maritime, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    Notes: no.68-114 (1968: June 13)
  - Item 9: Todd Daily Maritime, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    Notes: no.68-115 (1968: June 14)
  - Item 10: Todd Daily Maritime, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    Notes: no.68-116 (1968: June 17)
  - Item 11: Todd Daily Maritime, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    Notes: no.68-117 (1968: June 18)
  - Item 12: Todd Daily Maritime, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    Notes: no.68-118 (1968: June 19)
  - Item 13: Todd Daily Maritime, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    Notes: no.68-119 (1968: June 20)